(Leonard:)Sheldon, you can't train my girlfriend
like a lab rat.
(Sheldon:)Actually, it turns out I can.
(Leonard:)Well, you shouldn't.
Oh, ugh.
There's just no pleasing you, is there?
(Sheldon:)You weren't happy
with my approach with her...
(Sheldon:)...so I decided to employ operant
conditioning techniques...
...building on the works of Thorndike
and B.F. Skinner.
(Sheldon:)Next week, I believe
I can have her jumping out of a pool...
(Sheldon:)...balancing a beach ball on her nose.
(Leonard:)No, this has to stop now.
(Sheldon:)I'm not suggesting we really make her
jump out of a pool.
I thought the "buzzinga" was implied.
(Sheldon:)I'm just tweaking her personality,
sanding off the rough edges, if you will.
(Leonard:)No, you're not sanding Penny.
Are you saying that I am forbidden
from applying a harmless...
(Sheldon:)...scientifically valid protocol
that will make our lives better?
(Leonard:)Yes, you're forbidden.